GOD'STIME EHISCHIOYA ATUEGBE

Address: 12 Wilbros Estate, chokocho, Etche LGA, Rivers state.

Graduate Electrical/Electronics Engineer || Instrumentation & Control Option || Python programmer

Email: godstimeatuegbe48@gmail.com || Mobile: +234-810-631-3407

OBJECTIVES

Dedicated and motivated Electrical Engineering graduate with 1.5 years of experience in power distribution systems, basic automation and controls with a good interpersonal relationship skill that would enable me to use my technical skills and leadership qualities for achieving the target and developing the best performance to the organization.

PERSONAL DATA

Date of birth: February 9, 2002

Sex; Male
State of origin: Edo state
Nationality: Nigerian
Marital status: Single

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Educational Institutions attended with dates and qualifications obtained:

Nigeria Maritime University, Okerenkoko, Warri, Delta state, Nigeria
 Bachelor of Engineering (B.Eng) – Electrical/Electronics Engineering
 CGPA: 4.32/5.0 (Second Class Upper division)

 Ritch Model Nursery, Primary and Secondary school, Eneka, Port-Harcourt, Rivers state 2013-2019

	West African Senior Secondary School Certificate (WASSCE/Senior WAEC)	2019
	Junior West African Senior Secondary School Certificate (Junior WAEC)	2016
•	Delightsome Pearl Nursery and Primary School, Eneka, Port-Harcourt, Rivers state	2016
	First School Leaving Certificate	2016

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

UNDERGRADUATE INTERN || SIWES

August 2023 – January 2024

Federal Airport Authority of Nigeria (FAAN) – Port Harcourt International Airport (PHIA).

- Received training in electrical equipment maintenance, airfield lighting maintenance, power distribution and management, domestic wiring, transformer and power transmission line maintenance.
- o Collaborated with the teams responsible for installing electrical signage on the airfield runways to enhance the lighting system and create illuminated pathways and directions for aircrafts.
- Entrusted with supervising fellow interns in managing the maintenance of the security lighting system at the FAAN Aviation Clinic facility.
- O Assigned with the responsibility to implement power distribution changes in the substations, as directed by the power house, to optimize power distribution efficiency across the airport.

o Drafted comprehensive reports and presentation summarizing my experience during the 6 months internship.

AWARDS, CERTIFICATION AND PROFESSIONAL AFFLIATIONS

➤ Automated solar powered electric fish dryer:

September 2024.

Nigerian Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (NIEEE) – Warri chapter.

Received a certificate of participation for presenting my team's project, titled "Automated Solar-powered Electric fish dryer". Representing my team at the NIEEE Warri Chapter Science, Technology, and Engineering week, I emerged as the first-place overall winner.

➤ Automated Electric fish dryer with solar input as backup:

October 2024.

Nigerian Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers – ICEPT Abuja 2024.

I was honored with a Plaque and a certificate of participation as the overall first-place winner for presenting my team's project, titled "Automated Electric fish dryer with solar input as backup". At the 20th International Conference and Exhibition on Power and Telecommunications (ICEPT) 2024, organized by the NIEEE during its 40th annual conference.

Affiliated Professional bodies:

Student Member, Nigerian Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (StMNIEEE).
 Warri chapter

2. Member, Society of Petroleum Engineers (MSPE). Nigeria Maritime University, Warri Chapter

2023 - Date

APPLICABLE SKILLS

- Computational & Statistical Skills:
 - Microsoft packages (MS Word, MS Excel, MS PowerPoint)
 - Basic knowledge in Python Programming (Jupyter Notebook, VS code, PyCharm)
 - Basic knowledge of Electronics Simulating softwares (NI Multism, Proteus 8 Professional)
- Teambuilding and staff supervision.
- Decision making.
- People management and organizational skill.

REFREES

1. Engr. Ezea Michael

H.O.D Electrical || Lecturer|| Nigerian Maritime University || Electronics Engineer|| +2348032667132

Relationship – Undergraduate Lecturer

2. Engr. Dr. Anughwure Akpofure

Dean of Engineering || Lecturer|| Nigerian Maritime University || AI Researcher || Telecommunication Engineer || +2347030562077

Relationship – Undergraduate Lecturer

3. Engr. Isaac Collins Febaide

Lecturer|| Nigerian Maritime University || Instrumentation & Control Engineer|| +2347069001875 Relationship — Undergraduate Lecturer